Wow
Vay be!
So many
Çok fazla var.
They're everywhere...
Her yerdeler...
Yes
Evet.
The memories of the youkai
Youkailerin hatıraları...
They haven't been able to relax and soar through the air like this
Onlar böyle rahatlayıp havada uçmayalı
For a long time
uzun zaman olmuştu.
Come with me
Benimle gelin.
You alright, little one?
İyi misin ufaklık?
You look a little nervous
Biraz gergin duruyorsun.
It's just...
Şey...
Paimon's never seen anything like this before...
Paimon daha önce hiç böyle bir şey görmemişti...
Whoa
Vay canına!
They've really blocked out the moon!
Gerçekten de ayın önünü kapattılar!
It does look a little intimidating
Biraz korkutucu duruyor,
Doesn't it
değil mi?
But I know them
Ama ben onları tanıyorum.
They may be loud and brash at times
Bazen gürültücü ve kaba olabiliyorlar.
But they are good and brave souls
Ama içlerinde iyilik ve cesaret var.
Even after losing their lives in a brutal war
Hayatlarını kanlı bir savaşta kaybettikten sonra bile
They have never given into grief or despair
kedere ve umutsuzluğa kapılmadılar.
Alas, their time is short
Ne yazık ki...
Do they...
Gitmeseler olmaz mı?
It's a feast
Bu bir festival.
And all feasts come to an end
Her festivalin bir sonu vardır.
Hehe
Hehe.
Since you're sorry to see them leave
Madem gittikleri için üzüldün
Why don't you do the recital along with me?
ayin sözlerini benimle söylemek ister misin?
"Oh, Hakushin, cause of this enchantment"
"Ey Hakushin, bu büyünün kaynağı!
"In reverence I perform this rite"
Bu ayini saygıyla
"To be a guiding light..."
yol göstermek için yapıyorum."
Wow
Vay canına!
So beautiful
Çok güzeller.
Look
Bak!
Lights are coming from Inazuma City!
Inazuma Şehri'nde ışıklar var!
The book says
Kitaba göre
Recite the secret spells of Lady Kitsune tonight
Leydi Kitsune'nin gizli büyüleri bu gece yapılırsa
And our wishes will come true...
dileklerimiz gerçekleşirmiş...
"Oh, Hakushin, cause of this enchantment"
"Ey Hakushin, bu büyünün kaynağı!
"I perform this rite, to be a guiding light"
Bu ayini yol göstermek için yapıyorum.
"Your unrivaled power..."
Benzersiz kudretin
"...will be honored eternally"
sonsuza dek onurlandırılacak."
Urakusai
Urakusai
You asked if I was doing well
İyi miyim diye sormuştun.
Really, every day is a happy day for me
Aslında ben her gün mutluyum.
But watching
Ama şimdi
You all leave now
hepinizin gittiğini görünce
I can't help but feel a little lonely
kendimi biraz yalnız hissettim.
Just a little, of course
Tabii çok değil.